Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as well,
so let's stay with the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending,
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our radar is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the many roads.
That come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow is waiting
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride the wave.
We're all together as well,
so let's see when it's done.
All our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our moths will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
Sorry if I caused you any disturbance.
Who the hell is that guy?
That's some power.
Must be a devil for him.
What kind?
Are you the proprietor
of this establishment?
Send the bill for any
repairs to this event.
What? What?
Don't tell me you're actually...
Perhaps I'll come by again soon.
I knew you were stronger than you let on!
What's your name, anyway?
I guess you could call it second sight,
but there's something that's telling me.
Not answering you would be
better for both our sakes.
Hey! What's your deal?
You blind or something?
My sincere apologies.
Did I hurt anyone?
Better for both our sakes, huh?
I got a feeling whoever
he is, he's infamous.
At least we know one thing for certain.
He ain't no ordinary guy.
Gah!
My bag's missing!
Oh, my watch is gone, too!
Nothing you want to see my wallet!
Oh, no!
Someone has stolen my favorite jacket!
It must have been after the
explosion when dust was everywhere!
He's infamous, all right.
That old man seems quite the thief.
There's only two here.
Was something taken from you as well?
One of my swords is missing!
My shoes was right here
a minute ago! What?!
You let him steal the treasure of Wano?
Looks like they stole from everyone.
But that's what fairies do for fun.
What are you babbling about?
Are the fairies a gang
of thieves or something?
Fairies are fairies, that's all I know.
All you can do is laugh and let it go.
Invisible fairies are the
guardians of Dressrosa
since ancient times and they're our ally.
When they engage in mischief, the
only thing to do is turn a blind eye.
Well, if fairies stole from
us, I guess that's okay then.
Are you all mental?
Oh, the Shusui is the national
treasure of the Wano Kingdom.
It's my sword, fair and square.
It belongs to my entire country.
Mark my words, one day
I shall duel with you!
so that I might return Shusui to Wano.
to the place it rightfully belongs.
I accept the duel and I
look forward to beating you.
You got too greedy, fairy.
You're not going anywhere.
Furo, where do you think you're going?
Get back here.
We don't have time to let you wander all
over this city chasing after a sword!
I like where this is headed.
Not you, Luffy.
Did you see the thief?
I will let none abscond from this place
with the national treasure of Wano!
I got my arm, Franky!
I want to be a part of this!
You want to settle down and
listen to my idea first?
What idea?
Now I understand.
And when it's just the
five of us on a mission,
I gotta step up and be
the adult of the group.
You just leave everything
up to your old pal Franky.
You're one of Doflamingo's
thugs, ain't ya?
I think this guy needs to be shown
what a real threat looks like.
Look, buddy,
how about you just spill the beans and
tell us everything we want to know, okay?
I swear I told you guys everything.
I remember being ordered to
chase around a couple of samurai,
right, but I don't recall how
they were caught or where?
they're currently being
held, and that's the truth.
Also, I don't have any idea what Smile is.
You sure you don't have
even the teensiest?
No, and this factory?
I don't know anything about that either.
Who are you people?
Man, what a bummer.
Even his own foot
soldiers are in the dark.
He's too far down the ladder
to know anything important.
Hey, tell us if we can find
someone higher ranking.
You're going to have
a hard time digging up
anyone else to interrogate in an alleyway.
Everyone's been summoned to
attend the Coliseum games.
Just look!
As you can clearly see, the entire
kingdom's headed over in that direction.
What direction?
To the Corridor Coliseum.
If you want high-ranking
officials, that's the place.
Why's that?
Because there's a huge
event going on today,
and all the family's leaders should
be in attendance watching it go down.
For whatever reason,
the young master is going to offer an
incredible prize to whoever wins the match.
Even I had my doubts
when it was announced.
It's the one thing everyone wants.
Don't tell me.
Is that delicious meat
bingo was talking about?
While he did say it's something you'd want,
it's probably more important than lunch.
It's not for children's eyes.
People are going to kill each other here.
Go home.
This is no mere event you're
going to witness today.
His Majesty has entrusted us
with the most extraordinary
prize to be awarded at the
conclusion of the game.
And would you like to know what it is?
First, let's go back.
There was a great warrior who
fought in the War of the Best.
He perished there two years ago.
The second division leader of the infamous
Whitebeard crew and son of
the King of the Pirates,
the one and only Fire Fist Age.
They say he could easily smash
through a warship with his
flaming punch and was able
to burn down an entire city,
reducing it to a hellscape.
Dear spectators,
I am proud to announce that
terrifying power has returned
to this world in the form of
a Devil Fruit once again Wait,
that's how it works?
That's crazy.
Feast your eyes.
The winner of today's event will receive
this forbidden fruit as their prize.
And it's a logia, the most powerful
type of Devil Fruit known to humankind.
The legendary flame flame fruit.
You're saying it's the real deal?
Doflamingo would never lie
about something this huge.
Is this fruit?
And it's so close.
Coliseum is packed with excitement today.
Our king has some of the
fiercest warriors from
the new world to sate your
gladiatorial pleasure.
To win, these warriors will put
themselves through the ultimate test
They'll have to earn it with blood, grit,
and pain For the defenders of this
tribe are no ordinary gladiators
The champion of each block will
have the fight of their life
Presenting the warriors
from the Don Quixote family
Our first warrior
Senor Pink, then Dellinger,
Lao G,
Mark Weiss,
and of course, the Colosseum's reigning
The big hero, Mr.
Diamante!
Start the fight already!
Yeah, we want to see some blood!
I don't get it.
How did Ace's Flame
Flame Fruit wind up here?
From what I've heard, each and
every Devil Fruit is unique.
There's never more than one
of each kind at the same time.
Although,
if the owner of the fruit's power dies,
Another Devil Fruit with the same power
will suddenly sprout up at some random
place somewhere in the world And the
next person who finds it and eats it,
they become the new holder of its power
After Firefist Ace died,
his flame flame fruit was reborn,
but nobody knew where until the
young master managed to hunt it down
Seems a bit crazy to offer up something
like that as a tournament prize,
but hey, who am I to judge?
Man, if I could get my
hands on power like that,
well, I'd carve out a
whole new life for myself.
Huh?
You're not getting
anywhere near that fruit!
Hey, wait a minute.
Don't you have an older brother named Ace?
I want it!
That fruit should be mine!
Oh, yeah.
You don't have any powers.
You could eat it.
Yeah, I'd rather not
lose my ability to swim.
Well, I can't eat it since I've
already got Gum-Gum powers.
But the idea of some random
stranger getting their hands on it,
no way, it's like a memento of them, huh.
There's a pretty good possibility
this is a trap especially with the
way Doflamingo taunted you with it
but there is one thing I'm sure of:
you can't let a chance like this
slip by you don't want to regret
something like that and besides we've
got business at the Coliseum so.
And let's make an appearance.
Heh-heh.
Look at those morons.
Think they can just walk off with it.
Probably get themselves killed.
They've got no idea what
they're about to walk into.
Yeah, ferry my ass.
It's nothing but a dirty thief.
To the right.
I told you to wait, dammit!
What?
Can't you forget about
a stupid sword or two?
I'd rather forget about your dumb ass!
Damn!
I'm not letting it get away!
What's that?
What, did you find the fairy? A fairy?
Such beauty!
Such passion!
You have truly the
world's fun, Miss Dunstan!
She's so beautiful!
You forget how stab-happy the
women in this country are?
A guy like you's gonna
wind up with holes in him.
She can stab me all she wants!
Crap, he's gone!
Bastard gave me the slip!
I'm so sick of that moss head!
But wait, this is the perfect chance
to leave him behind on this island.
I mean I tried to catch him.
No one can argue with me on that
Nothing,
but couples around here like the whole
damn town's trying to make me jealous jeez.
Excuse me.
I need your help.
Hold me in a romantic embrace. What?
You see where she went?
We can't lose her.
I know she slipped out the back
door into Lover's Lane here.
She couldn't have gone far.
We'll find her.
Do not let her leave town.
Right!
I think they're gone now.
Thank you so much.
Sir, it's okay.
You can release me now.
Believe me, the pleasure
was entirely mine.
Are you alright?
Did I bump your nose
with my head, perhaps?
No.
The only impact I felt was
the shock of meeting you.
Are you sure?
That's so much blood. No, no.
Really, it's nothing.
But it must hurt.
I've fallen off a cliff into the
bottomless abyss of love. What?
Please, no, you shouldn't say such things.
I ignore you, for I've
already given up on love.
Any man I've ever been
involved with was...
Yes, they were all able to die happy men.
Those goons back there, who were
they and why were they chasing you?
If there's anything I can do
to help, just say the word.
Those men were the police.
I'm afraid there was a
man, and things between us.
They went sour, and then I stabbed him.
What you're saying? It's true.
The women here are so passionate.
That they stabbed for love.
Okay, you're okay with stabbing?
No, what's wrong?
You must stop.
I beg you, not to indulge
this wicked woman.
What don't take that risk?
I might fall in love with you.
And once we arrive, there is a man
there I need you to kill for me.
Looks like the place.
Whoa, that coliseum is huge!
The crowd's going nuts in there.
Makes me want to sign
up for the competition.
Yeah, listen to all that.
Damn, fugitive toy.
Get away from the coliseum.
One of these days, we're
going to catch you.
Keep trying, you suckers.
Jetwalk!
You are too slow! Look!
My foot is placed in the Coliseum.
I don't really need to
remind you of the law, do I?
As you both know, the police and the
Navy are forbidden from entering here.
It doesn't matter if
you're chasing a criminal.
This is not your jurisdiction.
The only rule of law within these walls
is that of the Don Quixote family.
If you choose to pull those triggers,
then you will be the ones thrown in jail.
Now be gone!
Dammit.
Oh my, elderly gentleman.
May I offer to carry
your belongings for you?
What the?
You sure got polite in a hurry.
You're one funny soldier.
Oh, am I?
Do you find me funny?
What about this?
Is this funny?
All right now, can you clear the path?
I'm sorry.
I was blocking your way.
Jeez, your face turned
as red as your coat.
You're a pretty serious guy
deep down, ain't you? What?
Of course I'm not.
Toys only exist to make people smile.
Well, there's no such
thing as a serious toy.
Now he's all mad.
Last chance to sign up.
Entries for the public are closing.
It's now or never.
Not like anyone actually has
the guts to enter this contest.
Cowards.
You see that, Luffy?
Looks like we just found
your ticket inside. Hm? Okay.
Hey! Over here!
I wanna enter!
I'm gonna enter me!
That geezer must be out
of his mind or something.
No way, he's saying.
Does he even know who he's
going to be battling against?
Not a chance.
From what I've heard,
they've got some heavy hitters from the
new world who are dying to get that fruit.
Listen up, Luffy.
You've got to promise me just one thing.
Fight however you want, but
don't let them know who you are.
I'm undercover.
Sign your name.
Luffy.
What did I just say?
This is the waiting room for competitors.
Stay here until we call you.
Talk about action central, wow!
The flame, flame fruit is as good as mine.
Think again, you blockhead!
Rrrrrrrr!
See that?
What's with the little guy?
Interesting!
Interesting.
Looks like we can use any weapon we want.
Huh?
What gives?
Is this some kind of joke? Hm?
I guess he's the final entrant.
Against warriors like us, get serious!
This is more than a joke.
It's an insult to every gladiator here.
What are you trying to pull, Squirt?
Think that fake beard
makes you look tough?
Forget about him, Spartan!
Who the hell wants to see the
weak get crushed to a bloody pulp?
The crowd thirsts for battles
between strong and manly warriors.
This is no place for the
likes of you, so piss off!
Here, let me help you!
I got a place!